<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Let&#39;s get clarity on Home</title>
    <link>https://aditigupta.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Let&#39;s get clarity on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aditigupta.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Listen to your heart or your head?</title>
      <link>https://aditigupta.info/posts/listen-to-your-heart-or-your-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aditigupta.info/posts/listen-to-your-heart-or-your-head/</guid>
      <description>If one knows even the basics of driving, you know that you can&amp;rsquo;t always drive with first gear or with the fifth for that matter. You got to switch gears as per the need. So how can you drive your life always on emotions or always with the mind? Remember to shift as per demand of the situation. This is the crux of this age old debate. I am sure that everyone faces this battle between head and heart and especially the folks between the age of 20 and 40.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jealousy has a cue</title>
      <link>https://aditigupta.info/posts/jealousy-has-a-cue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aditigupta.info/posts/jealousy-has-a-cue/</guid>
      <description>You would rarely know any individual who has not felt jealous ever in life. Its not an uncommon tendency for people to feel the dearth when they see others as complete or successful or abundant. But how they carry forth this feeling depends upon an individual’s mental capability. Based upon people’s reaction to jealousy triggers, I categorise people in 3 groups:
(i) Perennial paucity - such people are mostly dissatisfied no matter what all they have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fools can create a paradise</title>
      <link>https://aditigupta.info/posts/fools-can-create-a-paradise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aditigupta.info/posts/fools-can-create-a-paradise/</guid>
      <description>Human brain is the most powerful machine that can ever exist. While the minds have potential to transform electrons into energy, it comes with a natural tendency to play safe. Your brain makes you defensive about your egos and thus makes it difficult for you to accept the unknown. Thus, you can be intellectually doomed.
“Stay hungry, stay foolish” said Steve Jobs at the Stanford commencement speech of 2005. He mentions how following curiosity and intuition turned priceless for him and, I believe, so it can for each of us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literacy versus Education</title>
      <link>https://aditigupta.info/posts/education-vs-literacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aditigupta.info/posts/education-vs-literacy/</guid>
      <description>Being an academician, I would love to talk about a topic closest to my heart. Acquiring degrees, being able to read and write, does not make you educated! Well, I mean it.
I am sure you have seen this- a queue of professionals waiting for a metro during the busiest hours, get pushing into each other as soon as the metro arrives. Or a very smart graduate man breaking into a ruthless argument over streets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s get clarity</title>
      <link>https://aditigupta.info/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aditigupta.info/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone,
I would like to introduce myself as Aditi Gupta, an academician, a writer and an experimenter.
Until present, I have meandered through the course of life and have thoroughly experimented en route. I have lived through the mirage, being open to experiences and with utter faith in heart, I have learnt miracles. I should have rather described myself as a perennial student though!!!
Befuddlement in me came with audacity that helped me to get clarity over a lot of things with deep insights.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
